

Shyam Bhetuwal

(+358) 453519888 | shyambhetwal@outlook.com |

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rshyamvetwal/ Helsinki, Finland

About me:

I am an IT Engineer with passion in Agile software industry. I am pursuing the opportunity which will allow me to grow professionally. I am certain that I can exceed your team's goals and expectations by using my skills, experiences and education.

WORK EXPERIENCE

13/03/2021 - 13/06/2021 - Oulu, Finland

RESEARCH AND DEVELOPMENT INTERNSHIP – OULU UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES

- > Worked in a diversed team.
- > Researched various ways to figure out solution for the project.
- > Developed a Web Application with better User Interface in React for student's project application.
- > Updated my skills in responsive web application development with React.

03/10/2020 - 28/12/2020 - Ireland

PROJECT TRAINEE - TECHNOLOGICAL UNIVERSITY DUBLIN(REMOTE)

- > Worked in a multicultural team remotely and developed a digital classroom android app.
- > Developed the application and completed testing and prepared the test document.

13/11/2019 - 28/03/2020 - Oulu, Finland

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER TRAINEE - PIIMEGA OY OULU

- > Added new features and refactored codes in ERP Timber pro application.
- > Figured out and fixed bugs, tested the codes and updated in SVN.
- >Worked with C#, .NET, SQL, Agile process, Scrum, Jira, SVN, MS Excel, MS Visual Studio, Microsoft SQL server management Studio and Babylon.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

21/09/2017 - 13/06/2022 - Oulu, Finland

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY – Oulu University of Applied Sciences

- * Programming languages like JavaScript, Java, SQL, C# and Python for different projects.
- * Database management systems like MySQL, MongoDB, MS Azure, MS SQL, MS Access and Google Firebase.
- * Frameworks and libraries like React, Node, Express, Flask, Cl,. Net, Numpy, Pandas, OpenCv etc.
- * Full Stack Web Application, Android and Hybrid application development as projects.
- * I used Git as a version control and Scrum/Jira as project management tool.
- * I studied different software testing methods and implemented those in projects.
- * Linux Operating System, Cloud Services, Networking and Security and IOT.

Address Yliopistokatu 9, Oulu, Finland | Website https://www.oamk.fi/en

DIGITAL SKILLS

Technical Skills, Programming Languages and Frameworks

SQL | React, Node, Express, .Net | C# and VB.net | MongoDb, MySQL | Python | HTML/CSS, JavaScript | Testing and troubleshooting | Agile Methologies | Testing and Verification | Internet Of Things | Git/Github | Microsoft office

Personal Skills

Collaboration and teamwork | Project plan, research and management | Analytical skills and abillity to solve problems | Fast Learning and Adaptability

PROJECTS

Individual Projects

- Ecommerce Shopping Cart App (React, Redux, Node.js, Express, Mongo Db and CSS)
- Library Management System (.Net, C#, Microsoft Access)
- Online Mobile Shop (React, MySQL, Node, Express, Bootstrap, Material-UI)
- Weather App (React native), Cordova weather app (React, CSS and Cordova)
- Live Video Streaming Robot (Python, Flask and different sensors)

GITHUB

Some of my learning projects

https://github.com/Shyamraja

LANGUAGES

Languages and proficiency level

- English (Excellent)
- Nepali (Native)
- Hindi (Good)
- Finnish (Basics)